Press play. Subtitles appear.
200+ languages. One app:  tryray.app
[slow. intriguing music playing]
[yoga instructor]
Take a deep breath in.
[Davis inhales]
[yoga instructor] And exhale.
[Davis exhales]
[yoga instructor] Inhale...
[Davis inhales]
[yoga instructor] And exhale.
[Davis exhales]
[yoga instructor]
Notice the beat of your heart.
The rhythm of life.
[scrubbing continues]
You hold the power to create
all that you desire
out of nothing.
You okay?
Yeah.
[yoga instructor]
What do you see?
What do you feel?
Remember that there is great
power within you.
[shutter and chain creaking]
And that power will guide you
on your journey.
Let me see the gun.
Is it loaded?
I suggest you load it.
[gun magazine clicks]
[yoga instructor] Today is a
beautiful day of opportunity.
I am exactly
where I need to be.
[sighs]
[alarm ringing]
[yoga instructor] I open
myself to the universe
and trust
in the unfolding of my life.
[sighs softly]
[yoga instructor] This day
will bring you peace
and an opportunity
for success.
[AI voice] Track your buddy.
[yoga instructor]
Feel this moment.
[engine starts]
[tires screech]
Have a beautiful
rest of your day.
[AI voice] You have
found your buddy.
[exhales softly]
[suspenseful music playing]
[exhales deeply]
Don't say anything
unless you have to. Okay?
[car beeping]
[beeping stops]
[clicking]
[bell buzzing]
[speaking Farsi] Are you good?
[Ben speaking Farsi]
Everything is good.
Who is this?
[in English]
This is my cousin.
[Sammy speaking Farsi]
Wasn't Leo your cousin?
[in English] No.
this is my other cousin.
Have you done this before?
Sat in a car for two hours?
Yeah.
[Sammy] Okay?
[Sammy speaking Farsi]
Put them in the case.
Come round the back.
I want to have a word.
[in English]
Ali. not you. stay here.
Just put the watches
in the briefcase. okay?
[exhales deeply]
[Masoud] What the...
[suspenseful music continuing]
Hey. what's the problem?
[breathing heavily]
[Davis] Hands on your head.
You're carrying a gun?
In the car.
- [Davis] All right. get in.
- What?
[Davis] Get in the trunk.
Masoud.
Where's your phone?
- In the car.
- [Davis] What's the PIN?
1324.
[Davis] There's
water in the trunk.
- [thuds]
- [panting]
[exhales sharply]
[Sammy speaking Farsi]
Today is different.
This isn't your usual run.
You're going to transport
two sets of diamonds.
Come closer.
[in English] Six diamonds.
Eight carats each.
[in Farsi] Total value.
3 million dollars.
What about the ones
in the briefcase?
They're fake.
- [in English] Fake?
- Get up.
[speaking Farsi] You need
to tie this to your leg.
And don't tell your cousin.
[phone dings]
Walk.
Yeah it's fine.
- [Sammy] Mmm-hmm.
- Mmm.
See that car
parked across the street?
He's gonna follow you
to Houghtons.
- [in English] Just for safety.
- Okay.
May I see your weapon?
What is this?
- It was my dad's gun.
- Oh. really?
Who was your dad? John Wayne?
Take this.
You bring it straight back.
No stopping.
What did I say?
[suspenseful music continuing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Ali] Guy's
fucking disrespectful.
[Angie] Hey. have you
seen my keys? I'm late.
Hey. can I get
a little privacy?
[Angie] If you're gonna take
a dump. then lock the door.
I'm peeing.
[Angie] You pee
sitting down now?
Best three minutes of my day.
[Angie] Jesus. that's sexy.
[radio host]
Back to the 405...
The 101 westbound
is clear now...
between Echo Park Avenue
and Thousand Oaks.
Not too bad through downtown.
but...
[breathing heavily]
[Ali] What the fuck?
It's your fucking house.
[Davis] Ben. as you can see.
my partner's
parked across the street
from your home.
It's just an insurance policy
same as the jewels
you're carrying.
also covered by insurance.
So let's not do
anything stupid. Understand?
When I say. "go."
slowly remove your gun.
both your phones.
and throw them into my car.
Clear?
Go.
Slowly.
Stay there. Do not move.
Ben. get out.
Kneel down back of the car.
Eyes forward.
Personally. I wouldn't die
for an insurance company.
Just take it and go.
[Davis] No. Ben. I want
the real diamonds
in the papers. Now.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I wanna get you home
to Soraya. Ben.
Help me do that.
[breathes shakily]
Where are they?
[exhales deeply]
- My ankle.
- [Davis] Which one?
[Ben] Left.
[Davis] All right.
slowly remove them.
Come on. Ben.
- Get out.
- [Masoud grunts]
Let's go. Fuckin' move.
Kneel down.
Here. I'm betting you didn't
back up your photos.
[Davis breathing heavily]
[gunshot]
- [Davis grunts]
- [car alarm beeping]
[Davis breathing heavily]
[Davis grunts]
- [engine revving]
- [tires screeching]
[panting. sniffling]
[grunting. panting]
- [grunts]
- [tires screeching]
[breathing heavily]
[car honks]
[tires screeching]
[car honking]
- [metal clangs]
- [Davis] Fuck!
[tires screeching]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[engine stops]
[breath trembling]
[siren blaring in distance]
[breathing heavily]
[swallows. grunts]
[intriguing music playing]
[car trunk thuds]
[engine starting. revving]
- [engine roars]
- [tires screech]
[Sharon] Wow.
Well. you have a very. uh.
- unique eye.
- [Monroe chuckles]
[Sharon] And your beautiful
home here is a real tribute
to all of your achievements.
What we offer you
is the highest level
of protection
for all of these things
- that you care so much about.
- Okay. Protection?
Come here.
What does this look like?
- Uh. a thermostat?
- Fingerprint activation.
All me and my daughter
have to do is touch it.
- Boom. Opens in a heartbeat.
- Oh.
- Okay. never seen that before.
- Panic safe.
One in every single room.
Well. that's not gonna lower
your insurance premiums...
but I'm certain
it must make you feel better.
It fucking well does.
I had two buddies last year.
had home invaders
while they were in bed.
- Really?
- You ever shoot one?
A home invader?
No. a Glock.
No. Well. that's not exactly
in my line of work.
You're gonna like it.
- No. no. no. No.
- No. it's gonna be good.
Here we go. You ready?
[sighs]
[Monroe] Hey. Ramon?
Could you please move?
Gracias.
I'm probably gonna hit him.
you know.
No. no. no.
You're not gonna hit him.
He gets out of the way
all the time.
All right. I'll take that.
and you take this.
And if you hit
one of those bottles...
I'll sign your policy
right now.
[Sharon breathes deeply]
Okay. [sighs]
Here you go. Just go ahead
and point... There you go.
All you do is relax.
and you just squeeze
when you're ready. okay?
- [gunshot]
- Oh! Oh. God.
[laughs] Well.
you didn't hit Ramon.
That's good. That's good news.
There you go.
All right. next up.
This needs
to be on the policy.
as it is definitely
appreciated
since I bought it.
I've only seen that
inside a museum.
[Monroe] Cost me
6.2 million dollars.
But we both know
contemporary Black art
is only going
in one direction.
Right?
Uh. listen. we got
a lot of stuff to go through.
We got a lot
of high-tech stuff in here.
[Sharon] What
makes us different.
is that we also
protect your privacy.
Um. for example.
we also have cyber liability.
Do you remember
the admission scandal
of a few years back?
- I do. yeah.
- [Sharon] Yeah. well.
none of our clients
were named in that.
And... hello.
We also will cover
your daughter's possessions
as she goes off to college.
That's my fiancée...
Adrienne.
[Sharon] Lovely to meet you.
We were just about to talk
about. uh. your coverage
for your wedding.
Sounds like
it's a beautiful venue.
[exhales deeply]
Are you gonna be long...
[sarcastically] "Daddy"?
[Monroe] No.
we're totally done here.
[Sharon sighs]
[radio host]
That's where gridlock.
- Getty Center Drive...
- Sharon.
[radio host] ...has the two
right lanes blocked
with the backup
starting at the 101.
Southbound Sepulveda will work
for you. getting from
- West LA to the airport.
- [Sharon sighs]
[rock song playing over radio]
[radio announcer] ...infused
with organic coconut.
aloe vera...
[Lou] Well. well. well.
right next to the 101.
Oh. don't fucking
start on that shit. Lou.
Jesus Christ. you ever gonna
swap out that shit bucket?
There's nothing wrong
with that shit bucket.
It's maturing
like a fine wine.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
[Tillman scoffs]
It's depressing.
is what it is. man.
I just. I can't understand
why you wanna
look so fucking poor.
[scoffs] That ain't
what poor looks like.
What do you care so much for?
Because I gotta be seen
riding in it with you.
Detective Buddha.
[Lou] Yeah.
What do we got here?
[Tillman] Round the back.
Courier got hit...
carrying three mil worth
of stones from downtown.
He just left these behind.
Ben?
What. he somehow knew
these were fakes or...
[Ben] I don't know.
[Tillman] We don't know.
Okay. What else
can you tell us. Ben?
He knew my wife's name.
[suspenseful music playing]
And how would he know that?
How the fuck
should I know. huh?
Why are you asking me
all this shit?
[chuckles] Easy.
Because. Ben.
the one day you're carrying...
nearly three mil in stones
is the day you get hit.
I mean. that's a little bit
of a coincidence. no?
Well. I didn't give him
any information
if that's what
you're asking. okay?
- [Tillman] I didn't say...
- You know what?
This is victim blaming.
what you're doing.
- Yes.
- [Tillman] I'm victim blaming.
- Is that what I'm doing?
- Did he take your phones?
Yeah. he did.
but he gave them back.
Your cousin says
you shot at him.
The gun fucking misfired.
He had a gun?
- Yeah.
- Why didn't he shoot you?
You'll have to ask him.
- Told you don't start on that.
- Start on what?
- That lone ranger shit.
- It's his M.O.. man.
What do you mean. "his M.O.?"
The M.O. of not leaving
clues behind?
He knows exactly what
they're transporting. when.
He cuts the camera line
in advance.
There's no violence.
He's in and out in seconds.
- or he disappears.
- Okay.
We're right next to the 101.
Come on. he's got rules.
- Rules? He's got rules?
- Yeah. and he sticks to 'em.
Yeah. this gonna
be another one
we eat shit for.
isn't it. Lou?
No one's eating shit.
- [Tillman sighs]
- What's goin' on with you?
[Tillman scoffs]
The lieutenant says...
I should look
into a change of partner.
Says if I stick with you.
I'll end up languishing.
[Lou] Did he?
[Tillman] Yep.
Well. what'd you say?
I told him
I didn't want to do that.
Thanks.
But this lone wolf
obsession of yours.
it ain't winning us
any friends.
It's the same guy.
and I know it.
Well. you better
be fucking right. Lou.
[engine starts]
'Cause I need to step up. man.
and soon.
[suspenseful music playing]
[sighs]
[Davis exhales deeply]
[paper rustling]
[breathing heavily]
[breath trembles]
- [Sharon exhales]
- [elevator bell dings]
[woman] Right next to Charles.
[indistinct chatter]
- [telephone rings]
- [man] No. no. no.
[exhales deeply]
[knocking on door]
[Phil] So how'd it go?
Did he show you his weapons?
Not all of them. I hope.
[chuckles]
[Sharon] It went good.
Did you close?
[Sharon] Yeah. basically.
He just. you know. wants to...
look over the quote.
Guy's like a gazillionaire.
He's got time for that?
Hey. I guess
that's how you stay rich.
Well. right.
Well. sure you nailed it.
Uh. Phil?
Yeah.
[Sharon] Any word
on the meeting?
What meeting would that be?
The partners' meeting.
The one
to finalize my partnership.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. um...
Yeah. no. the. uh...
I just gotta get the senior
team around the same table.
but Mark is just back from
Maui. so let me chase it up.
Yeah. but that's what you said
before he left.
Yeah. well. I'm not in charge
of calendars. Sharon. so...
- Well...
- Can we not?
[sighs]
[sizzling]
[indistinct chatter]
[Money] So how'd it go?
Uh...
There was. uh. an incident.
Police?
Nah. just some kid.
you know. it nearly went...
I don't know.
Do you believe in omens?
Fuck omens.
You got shook up. that's all.
This and the next one
in Santa Barbara.
you'll have had a good year.
And you'll have
a good year. too.
and I'm taking all the risk.
You're just selling it.
Something bothering you?
It's just the Santa Barbara
job. you know.
it doesn't feel right.
That's a lot of money
to leave on the table. champ.
I have a buyer waiting.
I know. but it's happening
in the middle of the day.
And we're going straight
in through the front door.
There's no way of knowing
how many people
will be in the car.
Someone could get hurt.
You got
something else in mind?
Yeah. working on something.
[Money] Well. good.
Now look.
go spend some money...
get laid. relax.
[Davis] See you later.
[Money sighs]
[line ringing]
[Ormon] Yeah?
Do you know who this is?
[intriguing music playing]
[door lock clicking]
Jonathan?
What happened to Sarah?
Sarah's not well tonight.
sweetie.
She said she messaged you.
Okay.
[softly] So what
do you like to do?
[Davis smacks lips hesitantly]
Uh. I don't know.
just. uh. normal stuff.
I guess.
[softly] That sounds nice.
[clothes rustling]
Are you an eye contact
or a no eye contact guy?
[exhales deeply]
[alarm chiming]
[yoga instructor]
Good morning.
May this day be a clean slate
for your mind...
for your actions...
for your thoughts.
May this day bring...
[Sharon sighs]
[sighs heavily]
[Mark] Uh. before we begin.
it is my pleasure to introduce
the latest member
of our valuation team.
Madeleine Adcock.
Along with Sharon.
Madeleine's gonna focus
on high net worth residential.
I'm sure we will all
make her feel welcome.
[team clapping]
Hey. guys. Thanks.
Thrilled to be here. guys.
[Mark] Um. okay. new business.
Sharon just valued
one of the wealthiest estates
in all of California
and what is likely to be
the most expensive wedding
we have ever insured.
What's the good word
for Monroe. Sharon?
Uh. it is promising.
[Mark] Okay.
Well. promising is good
but closed is better.
[laughter]
Uh. next up is Phil.
What do you got?
Yeah. something fishy
on the claims side.
Seven-figure claim
from a jeweler. Samir Kassem.
Courier gets robbed
the one day in years if ever
he's transporting three mil
in diamonds. [scoffs]
- [Mark] Yeah.
- Big coincidence. right?
[Mark] Big coincidence.
Sharon. think maybe you could
work your charms with
one of our friends in blue.
get him to polygraph
the vendor?
This week?
I was planning
to follow up with Monroe.
- So...
- It's a seven-figure claim.
[Phil] Okay. how about
we have Madeleine
take over the follow-up
with Monroe?
You know.
fresh face. fresh approach.
[Mark] Good idea. Phil.
[Madeleine] Yeah. I'd be happy
to take it over.
If that's okay with you.
Yeah. sure.
[Mark] Okay. next.
uh. international...
Sammy. you can
see how this looks.
- right?
- No.
No. I don't. No.
Okay. what is this? Hmm?
Fat cop. bad cop?
When do you think
- I started this business?
- [Tillman chuckles]
I opened my store 27 years ago
and I got two other stores.
Why in the world
would I cheat on my own...
[Lou] Okay. let's calm down.
Did you call him...
- [sighs]
- ...to tell him when to expect
the courier?
No. I emailed.
[suspenseful music playing]
So now what you gotta
ask yourself is...
"How does he know
whose email to hack?"
And how could he know
who's intending
to transport something
before they transport it?
It's the same
as last time. email.
calendar. Facebook.
WhatsApp. Instagram.
What. no Snapchat? TikTok?
She's too old for that.
[camera clicks]
- [engine revving]
- [vehicles honking]
[rap song playing]
[sighs]
[song stops]
Boo. [chuckles]
[Money clears throat]
[Money] There's a job...
- up in Santa Barbara.
- [Ormon] Mmm-hmm.
My guy has laid it all out
but he's not doing it.
Why ain't he doing it?
He's lost his nerve.
I've seen it before.
He thinks
someone could get hurt.
[Ormon chuckles]
[Ormon] Mmm.
[Ormon inhales deeply]
My dad always said. "You gotta
break a few eggs." so...
Oh. you're not your dad.
God rest his soul.
You might not have the stomach
for some of the things he did.
But if you want
a chance to find out...
this is it.
You think you can handle it?
[indistinct radio chatter]
[suspenseful music continuing]
- [tires screech]
- [car thuds]
- [alarm beeping]
- [mumbling] Oh...
[Maya] Fuck!
Fuck.
Fuck. man.
why'd you stop so suddenly?
I stopped. but there's
nothing sudden about it.
Red light.
- [Maya sighs]
- You okay? You...
No. I'm not okay. I'm late.
and this is my boss's car.
Um... Shit. I just. can I...
I need to get
your insurance information.
Yeah. uh...
Listen. why don't...
Take this and that should
cover the damage.
We don't have to worry about
the whole insurance.
What? You just
have this wad of cash
you wanna pay to not
have the hassle? I don't...
I'm trying to help you out.
You crashed into me.
[sputtering]
I appreciate that.
but I have to go through
the proper channels.
Otherwise I'm gonna get fired.
Let me get a pen.
Yeah. right.
[Maya] Fucking thousands
of dollars in your pocket?
- [sighs]
- [car door closes]
[Maya sighs]
Okay.
Sorry.
[Davis] Um...
[Maya sniffles]
- Here you go.
- Well. okay.
You got. uh. kids?
- What?
- There's a car seat.
Oh. uh...
No. No. God. They're. um...
- It's my boss's car.
- Oh. yeah. Yeah.
She's got a pair of twins.
They're pieces of shit.
Yeah. I don't
have kids either.
- Um...
- Okay.
Um. I guess
someone will be in touch.
I don't know
- how this works. so...
- Great. Yeah. you know...
See you later.
[sighs]
Excuse me. Hey. I guess
you're the insurance lady?
Ah. And I guess
- you're the detective man?
- Yeah.
Sharon Coombs.
- Thanks for meeting with me.
- Sure.
- Want one of these?
- Nah. no. thanks. I'm good.
You don't like smoothies?
I don't even like
to say the word "smoothie."
[Sharon] Mmm.
So you got something for me
on the Kassem case?
Actually. we were hoping
you would consider
polygraphing Kassem
and the courier.
Why. so you could deny
his insurance claim?
He paid his premiums.
What do you wanna do?
You wanna screw him in return?
That's a nice job
you got there. Sharon.
- Yeah? And how's...
- Nice.
...public service
working out for you?
All you hoped it would be?
I mean. you do make
the world a safer place
so. I guess that's
job satisfaction for you. huh?
Least I'm not screwing
the people
I'm paid to protect.
I'm not screwing over anybody.
What we provide
is what people want most
in the world after wealth.
- Wouldn't that be good health?
- Nope.
That's security of wealth.
Ah. damn it. And here
I was brought up to believe
that money
can't buy you happiness.
I'm sorry. You've been misled.
Studies show that happiness
in the over-45s
is overwhelmingly tied
to financial security.
I'm just talking
about a comfortable life
in a nice.
little neighborhood.
Got your piece
of the American pie. Sharon?
I live here by the beach.
Why else would anybody
wanna live in this town?
You know. statistics point
to this being an inside job.
- Statistics?
- Yes.
Every series of human actions
creates a pattern.
Now. I could show you a map
that would predict
where 90% of the people
who develop heart disease
will live in LA
and I can tell you...
it's nowhere around here.
It's science.
- Nice to meet you. Sharon.
- It's nice to meet you. too.
And. you know.
we are well within our rights
to polygraph.
[suspenseful music playing]
[engine idling]
[Lou] Every series
of human actions
creates a pattern.
The area you're looking at
has seen 219 robberies
in the last four years.
Arthur. can you please remove
every robbery under 500K?
[projector beeps]
- Boom.
- [Fellner] Ooh. CSI.
[laughter]
Go ahead. Just here to listen.
Remove every robbery
that doesn't involve
a courier delivery service
- or an armored vehicle.
- [projector beeps]
Now remove every robbery
where there was some type
of violence used in a crime.
[projector beeps]
Lastly. remove every robbery
where there was
some DNA or evidence
left at the scene.
[projector beeps]
Boom.
As smart as our guy is.
he can't help
but form a pattern.
He knows when the jewelers
are moving merchandise
and when...
I believe by hacking
their communications.
He doesn't use violence.
In every single case
he hits along the 101 Freeway.
Last time was south.
I bet the next time is north.
[car door closes]
[suspenseful music playing]
[car honks]
[door release buzzes]
[Ormon] Get the fuck down!
[people gasping]
- [Ormon] Give me the case!
- What?
- [Ormon grunts]
- What the fuck?
[grunting]
- [Ormon] Hey. you. hands up!
- [women gasping]
Get your fucking hands up!
- Hey. come here!
- No.
[Ormon] Come here!
Get on the fucking ground.
Is there anyone in back?
Is there anyone
- in the fucking back?
- No!
There's nobody in the back.
There's nobody there.
[Ormon panting]
[baby cries]
[Ormon] There's no one
in the fucking back. huh?
There's no one
in the fucking back?
[woman exclaims]
[Ormon] Shut up!
- You. where's the key?
- I don't have it.
[Ormon] Where's
the fucking key?
[Grant] It's outside.
It's in the car!
It's in the car outside.
[Ormon] Where's
the fucking key?
- [Grant] It's in the car.
- [Ormon] What fucking car?
[Grant] It's outside.
[Ormon] Fuck!
You think I'm playing games?
Give me... the fucking... key!
- Or I fucking kill you!
- Okay. it's on my neck!
I'll give it to you.
[Ormon] Now! Fuckin' over it!
- [Grant] Take it!
- [Ormon] Come on!
[Grant] Just. it's...
You're fuckin'...
[baby continues crying]
[Ormon] Someone
shut the baby up.
What?
[grumbles]
You. open
the fucking cabinets!
What the fuck? What is the...
- Unlock it!
- I don't work here!
I don't work here!
I don't work here! No!
- [man] Doesn't work here.
- I don't work here!
- [Ormon] Sit the fuck down!
- [woman exclaims]
[Ormon] Okay. go around.
unlock it. Now!
Don't you fucking look at me.
- Open the... Open it.
- It's open.
Put it in the bag.
Hurry up! Come on!
Come on.
Come on!
Come back around!
Get the fuck
back on the ground!
Hurry the fuck up!
You. come here!
Lay on him! Lay on him!
Get the fuck on top.
Stay.
[grunts] Fuck.
Where's the fucking
door release?
- It's next to the till!
- [Ormon] What?
[baby continues crying]
[Ormon groans]
[woman sobbing]
[Ormon] It's where?
Where? Where the fuck?
[door release buzzes]
[Ormon] It's okay. shut up.
- [door rattling]
- Fuck! Fuck!
Fucking... Fucking...
You. get the door! Now!
- [gunshot]
- [all scream]
[Ormon] Open the fucking door!
Okay. okay. okay.
Easy. Easy.
[alarm ringing]
- [door release buzzing]
- [Ormon] Remember...
I know what you look like.
Fucking take care
of your baby.
[baby continues crying]
[Stewart] Give us
the room a minute.
- Cap.
- Ray.
[Lou] Hmm.
[door closes]
So what's your objective?
- What do you mean?
- [Stewart] You just turned
a bunch of random robberies
into a series.
You understand what that means
for the department. right?
I understand
that we're gonna have to...
Let me finish. Let me finish.
Two of your little...
examples there are cases
that already have suspects.
Another one
was closed by Fellner
six weeks ago. you understand?
Uh...
Yeah. but he was wrong.
No.
No. he wasn't wrong.
He went from
red to black on the board.
That's never wrong.
You know what we don't do?
We don't reverse
our fucking clearance rates.
That's wrong.
But I know I'm right.
because all of these
are the same guy
and he doesn't
let himself get caught.
Right. right. [chuckles]
Your one brilliant factor
tying these all together...
your guy's untraceable.
Oh. come on.
You and I both know
there's nothing here
that's random.
Stop talking.
[chuckles] Okay.
[Stewart] Okay.
You got the lowest
clearance rate on the squad.
It's pulling everyone down.
me included.
What's the matter with you?
You used to be the...
You should've been sitting
in my seat by now. man.
Play the game.
Find a theory
that works
for the whole building.
[door opens. shuts]
[phone chimes]
- [phone chimes]
- [intriguing music playing]
[phone dings]
[phone clatters]
[woman 1] And he
bought me flowers...
[woman 2] Remind me again
what it is you do.
[man 1] It's basically
software sales to banks.
[man 2] Blanquette
de veau here
apparently is superb.
I mean...
[Maya clears throat]
- [Maya] Hey. sorry I'm late.
- Hey. That's okay.
I crashed into someone
and those things
take a long time to sort out.
[sighs]
I'm guessing
he stopped too fast. huh?
You know what? He did.
and it was fully his fault.
but I got another
hot date out of it. so...
[Davis chuckles]
- [mumbles]
- [Maya clears throat]
Do you come here a lot?
Uh. couple times. yeah.
Couple of times.
The. um...
The blanquette de veau
is. it's good.
Supposed to be good.
Are you. um...
Are you in LA?
- Uh... I move around a lot.
- Do you?
Yeah. For work.
What is it you do?
Basically. uh...
software development...
Um...
for banks. It's sales.
It's not very interesting...
No. it's cool.
[Davis] Yeah.
[Maya clears throat] Mmm.
You okay?
[hesitantly] Yeah. Um...
I think maybe
this wasn't a great idea.
You seem super great
and you're very...
Uh... [chuckles] But I. um...
I honestly just don't see us
having all that much...
in common.
And I kind of have a rule
where if it doesn't feel right
you just don't waste
each other's time.
What... But how do you know?
How do I know what?
That we won't have
anything in common.
Uh...
Well. I have no idea
what blanquette de veau is.
I mean. I would just...
I would never come
to a place like this.
[Davis] Yeah...
me neither.
Really?
I've never been here before.
[chuckles] You've never
been here?
Just thought it was the kind
of place that people...
[clears throat]
...you know. take people.
[Maya] Um...
I think it's veal.
What?
Blanquette de veau.
- Oh. Oh. veal. [chuckles]
- [Davis] Yeah.
Yeah. I. um...
No. I would not eat that.
- Definitely not.
- What would you eat?
[Lou sighs]
I thought we loved each other.
Yeah. we do.
But more in a force of habit
kind of way. right?
I mean. don't you want
something you can
be excited about?
- Something new?
- [cellphone buzzing]
You can get it. Go.
No. I'm fine. I don't need to.
- [Angie] Pick it up.
- No. I'm not picking it up.
Is it your first?
Affair?
Do you really wanna know?
[scoffs]
I'm gonna move out
at the weekend.
No. you know what?
You stay. I'll move out.
Where are you gonna go?
Maybe I'll move to the beach.
The beach?
Are you serious?
You're the least
beach person I know.
I'm way more beach
than you are.
[Angie] Bullshit.
[Maya] "How did your
last relationship end?"
Work. I had to move.
"What motivates you?"
Money. I guess.
[Maya sighs]
What?
Okay. um...
"Have you ever
used handcuffs?"
Yeah.
Okay.
Uh. "If you had the option
to press a button..."
Oh. "...and start your life
over. would you press it?"
Yeah.
You would?
[Davis] Mmm-hmm.
You?
No.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
I mean. it's kinda...
What?
Sad?
Okay. look.
I work for a publicist
and we work with musicians
and actors and stuff
and like...
I swear to you.
it doesn't matter
how much money they make
it's never enough.
I'll know when I have enough.
How?
I have a number in mind.
but. uh...
I know it's just enough
to feel...
well...
safe.
So you think
maybe. uh. you wanna...
- Meet up again?
- Yeah.
[Maya] Hmm.
Maybe.
Yeah?
Yeah.
[reporter] ...armed with
a semi-automatic weapon
terrorized the staff
and customers
in an extremely
violent assault
in which shots were fired.
It happened in Santa Barbara
at a high-end jeweler
in the Central
commercial district
a little after 10 a.m.
The intruder was captured
by surveillance cameras
but is said to have worn
a motorcycle helmet
throughout the robbery.
This follows a string
of high-profile robberies
in Southern California.
[woman] I don't work here!
I don't work here!
[Lou] Okay. pause it.
[woman] No. no. no!
Uh. can we interview
your witnesses?
They're not gonna
be able to give you much.
The guy was wearing
a motorcycle helmet
the whole time.
One of 'em shit their pants.
Literally.
Shit in his pants.
Well. well. well.
The 101 robber.
There he is. Lou.
[sniffles]
Yeah.
something doesn't add up.
- I'm sorry. what?
- Just...
What do you mean. "Something
doesn't add up." Lou?
You said
he was gonna hit north.
Boom. He hits north. okay?
We're barely a mile
from the 101.
so the location fits.
the target fits.
the M.O.. it fits. Lou.
So. which...
I'm sorry. which bit
doesn't add up?
Our guy never hurt anyone.
[indistinct chatter]
Ah. here's my champ.
What you got going?
Where's my account
for the last job?
Why? What's the matter?
Santa Barbara
was the last job.
Oh.
Santa Barbara.
[Davis] Yeah. I found it.
I planned it.
I walked you through it.
And you said
you didn't wanna do it.
It wasn't yours to give away.
You want a cut. is that it?
It's not about
the fucking money.
Well. then what is it about?
It's about trust.
This happens again.
I think you and I are done.
You and I are done?
You're gonna threaten me now?
Maybe you wanna have a think
about where you'd be
without me. huh?
Yeah.
I'll be here
when you come back
with your tail
between your legs!
[Sammy] Is this how you treat
all your customers
or it's a special treatment
for immigrants?
[Sharon] This is just
a formality. Mr. Kassem.
If you have nothing to hide.
then you've got absolutely
nothing to worry about.
[Sammy] Oh. it's a formality.
You know. what I object to
is not that I pay you
to insure me
and you look for ways
to refuse
to give what you owe.
it's that with this machine
you're saying
not only.
"We think you're a thief"
but also.
"We think you're a liar."
You know. Ms. Coombs.
those people you work for.
they're all parasites.
Are you also a parasite?
[intriguing music playing]
[Ormon grunts]
My guy. he's...
planning something new.
I need you to find him
and I need you to follow him.
Here's someone
he gets information from.
He's a Google guy
or something.
You watch him. he'll show up.
Then what?
You're not gonna rob
the courier.
You let him do that...
and then you'll rob him.
[breathing heavily]
[Davis sighs] "Step mom
butt sex dot com"?
It's just
the encryption location.
- Follow the steps.
- [Davis] Hmm.
Yeah. it's funny what just
floats to the top
of the old mind. huh?
Thanks.
[chuckles]
[exhales sharply]
[indistinct chatter]
[Sharon] White Mercedes GLE.
please.
Yes. ma'am. Coming right up.
It's a cool car.
[Sharon] Thanks.
Life's too short
to drive boring cars. right?
Elvis? He said that.
Ah. right.
And what did he drive?
See. that would be
a gold Cadillac.
[both chuckle]
Makes sense.
You into cars?
Ah. I like the ones
with a bit of character.
Would that be old ones
or new ones?
Today. an old one.
[Sharon] Today?
I need to be
in your line of work.
[both chuckle]
So what are we driving today?
[sighs] If you can guess.
I'll give you the keys to it.
Ooh.
Be careful.
I'm good at this.
- Yeah?
- Mmm-hmm.
All right.
Okay. I'm gonna go with
a Chevy Chevelle.
Color?
Racing green.
Right color.
Well. one out of two.
that's not bad.
[Davis] Not bad at all.
[Sharon] That is
a beautiful car. though.
I underestimated you.
Mike.
Sharon.
Nice to meet you. Mike.
[Davis] Nice to meet you. too.
- [door closes]
- [engine starts]
[key clacking]
- [operator] Like I said...
- [Tillman] No...
[operator] ...that's
the last image we have.
[Lou] Are you certain
that we don't pick him up
on the 101
in either direction?
[operator sighs]
Still certain.
Somewhere between that turn
and the 101. he switched cars.
Why are you so convinced
he took the 101?
Hey. don't ask. man.
Look. there's 30 blocks
between there and the 101.
- Let's get lookin'.
- Are you serious?
- [Lou] I'm serious.
- Lou. come on. man.
[Lou] How else
are we gonna find him?
[Maya] The books
come with the place?
- Uh-huh.
- [Maya] Huh.
For someone
who likes things...
you don't
really have a lot of...
personal stuff.
No photos of family or...
Do you have any?
What? Photos?
[chuckles] No. Family.
Yeah. someplace.
Someplace?
- What. like in a drawer?
- [Davis chuckles]
I don't know. we're just
not really that kinda family.
Don't really keep in touch.
I don't know.
Do you have.
like. brothers? Sisters?
- Mom? Dad?
- [knife clangs]
Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know.
we didn't really. uh.
have a lot of stuff growin' up
and whatever we did have.
I didn't really
keep any of it.
So...
[mellow music playing]
What?
Mystery man.
Yeah.
[Maya] Can I turn on
some music?
[Davis] Yeah.
There's a thing in the corner.
Do you have a favorite song?
Um...
[Maya] No. Okay.
I don't know why I would ask
why you would have
a favorite song.
[Davis] Suppose that's
another black mark. huh?
[Maya chuckles]
[Maya] Aye. yai. yai...
- Do you. um...
- [device beeps]
Do you listen to music or...
Yeah. sometimes.
[soft rock song playing]
[Maya] Sometimes?
You don't. do you?
Come on.
I can't dance.
Come here.
No photos.
no music. no dancing.
Someone needs to teach you
how to be a human.
Yeah.
[Maya laughs]
[crowd cheering
over music player]
Ah.
I love that.
They cheer for home.
but no one does that for LA.
[crowd cheering
over music player]
[song fades]
[Maya] Happy?
Yeah.
Scared?
Yeah. maybe.
[exhales]
[mellow music playing]
You're not gonna stay?
[exhales softly]
[Maya] Do you want me to stay?
[Davis] Yeah.
Good.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[tense music playing]
[engine starts]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[panting]
[Davis grunts]
[line beeps]
[Davis] Hi. this is Mr. Stone.
I need a new apartment
on the beach
available immediately.
[door thuds]
[doorbell buzzing]
[Devon] Can I help you?
[Ormon] Got delivery
for Wilson.
I'm not expecting anything.
[Ormon] It's got
your name on it.
All right.
Just leave it outside.
[Ormon] I'm not allowed
to do that.
[sighs] All right.
Leave it in the hall.
[door buzzes]
- [door thuds]
- [Devon] Whoa!
[Devon gasping]
[Ormon] Move.
Come on. move. Move.
[both grunting]
Huh?
You're gonna tell me what you
fucking gave him. okay?
Fucking tell me.
[panting]
[Tillman] How many
more of these
fucking garages you gonna
make us do tonight. man?
[Tillman sighs]
Hey. man...
- Let's take a look.
- Have you...
- See there?
- What? Now what?
Lou.
[car alarm beeping]
[sighs deeply]
Fuck's sake. man.
[mumbles] Mmm. Huh.
Call forensics.
[man] Black
wasn't a color for him.
It was his whole subject.
[woman] I wouldn't
put it on my wall
but I do love
the sense of drama.
I think you can be confident
it's not gonna lose its value.
The real question is...
how much do you love it?
Well. I love it.
It'll go great
with the new chairs. you know.
[Andrew] Really?
You sure you want this guy
glaring down at us
every time we have dinner?
[Beth] He's not glaring.
[Andrew] He's glaring.
[Beth] I'm sure.
And he isn't glaring. really.
He's just looking. you know.
Excuse me.
I'll be right with you.
- [Beth] Okay.
- Sure. Thank you.
Well. what a coincidence.
[Davis] Hey.
Uh. Sharon. right?
- [Sharon] Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Mike?
- That's it.
- Yeah. good to see you.
- [Sharon] Hmm.
Uh...
So do you collect art
like you do cars. Mike?
Uh. not really. but I like it.
I like the sense of drama.
[glass clinking]
[Sharon] Hmm.
Hey. do you maybe
wanna get out of here?
Grab a drink or something?
[Tillman] I swear. man...
you divorced guys.
you always think
you're gonna move to the beach
and meet
some hot surfer chick.
What you gonna do?
Take up surfing?
No. I'm gonna...
Thinking of doing the yoga.
The yoga?
[Tillman laughs]
'Course. you are. What kind?
They got kinds?
Big time. man.
They got hot yoga. fast yoga.
street yoga. Greek yoga.
- Greek yoga?
- That last one might be food.
[Tillman chuckling]
So. you just wanna get laid.
Oh. man. I wanna get fit.
- Fitness?
- [sighs]
- Please. booze man. you...
- [Lou] What's up?
It's like a new car.
Fuck.
Except for one
microscopic speck of blood.
[Tillman] Is it enough
to get DNA?
[forensics officer] Should be.
Let me see.
[Davis] So. I guess
you work in the art world?
[Sharon] Nope. Less glamorous.
I write insurance policies
for people
who have more money than
they know what to do with.
[Davis] So. you must know
a lot about
what things are worth. huh?
Mmm-hmm. Too much.
But I also have to know a lot
about the people
that own these things.
How do you mean?
[Sharon] You know.
are you a thrill seeker.
are you an alcoholic.
do you gamble.
do you cheat on your partner?
You know. all those questions
that you can't ask
but you obviously need to know
the answers to.
So. you get real good
at reading people.
And what have you.
uh. read about me?
[Sharon chuckles]
Mmm-mmm.
Things you don't like or what?
[Sharon] Mmm-mmm.
Nope. No. did not say that.
[Sharon chuckles]
Come on.
Okay.
[sighs] Well. you look like
a person who has secrets.
- Is that right?
- [Sharon] Mmm-hmm.
Your shirt's new
or newly pressed
which says you don't
do your own laundry
or you're a bit OCD.
Uh. you're very groomed.
Your hair. your nails.
your 12-thousand-dollar
watch there.
everything is just. uh...
a little too perfect.
Which tells me
you have a lot of money
and a lot of time
on your hands. Mike.
Got the clothes. the cars...
but you can't seem
to look me in the eye.
And I'd bet
you didn't grow up with money.
How do you figure that?
Because people who grow up
in chaos crave order.
You talkin' about me or you?
Maybe both.
That hit too close to home?
No.
I have a...
[clears throat]
I have a confession to make.
[Sharon] Really?
[laughs] I haven't even
finished my drink.
This wasn't a coincidence.
Us meeting again.
Oh.
I came here to talk to you.
You followed me?
I came here to make you
a business proposition.
You see. I know some things
about you. too. Sharon.
Really? Like what?
You live alone.
You're not married.
You never have been.
No children.
You've worked at the same
company for 11 years.
You're a VP when you
should be a partner.
Uh-huh. Who the fuck are you?
[Davis] Just give me
30 seconds.
No. I...
[Davis] What
I have to offer you
is zero risk to you
and a huge upside.
a life-changing upside.
- No. that's okay. That's okay.
- [Davis] What I do...
is I take certain pieces
of information
from people like you
and those
ultra high-value items
belonging to the rich guys
you mentioned?
Well. I occasionally
make them disappear.
But I do it in a way
that no one can trace it.
no one gets hurt...
except maybe the shareholders
of companies like yours.
Yeah.
So. you're a thief?
I get it.
Let me tell you something.
Mike.
I've gotten where I've gotten
through hard work.
I don't lie. I don't steal.
and I certainly don't cheat.
And I'm not
about to start now.
Guys you work for. you think
they're squeaky clean?
Mark made partner
in five years.
- How do you think I know that?
- [sighs]
I mean. you really think those
guys give a fuck about you?
Have a nice life. Mike.
Hey. if you change your mind.
just post a photo of a beach
on Instagram.
and I'll know
to come find you.
Look. I don't know
if anybody's
ever told you this.
but you live a fucked-up life!
[door opens]
[door closes]
[suspenseful music playing]
[engine roaring]
[engine whirring]
[yoga instructor]
Take a moment
to check in with yourself.
[exhales deeply]
Check in and see
where you may be holding onto
tension in this very moment.
[engine revving]
[tires screech]
[tires screeching]
[engine roaring]
[yoga instructor] Check in
with your breath.
your body.
Consciously breathe
this tension out.
Breathe it out.
- [tires screech]
- [horn blares]
[yoga instructor] Let your
heart open up to the presence
of love all...
[exhales]
[bus brakes hissing]
- [engine idling]
- [panting]
[engine revving]
[tires screeching]
[tires screech]
[Davis breathing heavily]
[engine revving]
[thuds]
[tires screech]
[car honking]
[metal scraping]
Oh. fuck!
[engine roaring]
[vehicles honking]
- [car honking]
- [grunts]
[tires screeching]
- [metal thuds]
- [Ormon grunts]
- Oh. fuck.
- [tires screech]
[breathing heavily]
[windshield clangs]
[panting]
[gate clangs]
[dog barking in distance]
[Davis grunts]
[man] Asshole.
You found me. Hoo!
- Who are you working for?
- [Ormon] Go away.
- Who you working for?
- Go away.
[can clatters]
Hmm? Huh?
Well. you know. I'm...
I'm pretty much in between
positions right now.
- Yeah?
- I'm looking to...
pursue
a career in hospitality.
- [Davis] Yeah?
- So yeah...
- What did he tell you to do?
- [Ormon] Who he?
[Davis] Yeah.
what did he tell you to do?
Your boyfriend? He?
[Davis] He tell you
to follow me?
Bro. I'm not gay.
[Davis] Hey.
stop fucking around.
- Did he tell you to follow me?
- Your boyfriend?
Your boyfriend?
Did he tell you to follow me?
Fuckin' touch me. I'm not gay.
[Davis] What'd he
tell you to do?
But if I was gay...
[Davis] What'd he
tell you to do?
Stop fucking...
- Who are you working for?
- Don't touch me.
- Answer the fucking question!
- Fucking touch me.
- Don't touch...
[clattering]
- Huh?
- Fuck you.
Quit fucking around. huh?
- You wanna kiss me?
- What did he tell you to do?
- Huh?
- [imitates kissing]
- What did he tell you to do?
[both grunting]
Hey! Fuck. Hey!
[groans]
Hey. hey. hey. All right.
- All right.
- Yeah? Huh?
Yeah. okay.
You tell him...
I see you again
- and you're both dead.
- Yeah.
- Understand?
- Yeah?
- Okay.
- You understand?
- Yeah. Okay.
[Ormon panting]
Okay.
All right.
Cool.
[helmet clatters]
[yoga instructor] Let go
of your past.
[can clatters]
Let go of your future.
Exist only...
in this moment.
Let's bring
our left foot forward
into our Warrior Two.
Let's reverse the Warrior.
Left elbow to left knee.
raising our right hand.
Let's go down to the floor...
raising our right hand
to the sky.
Gaze toward the sun.
the source of all life.
- Hey.
- [Sharon] What are you doing
here. detective?
What a coincidence.
Is it?
This keeps happening to me.
[scoffs] Of all the lousy
yoga joints in LA.
You either had a drastic
change of circumstance
or you're stalking me.
[chuckles]
Just trying something new.
Trial separation?
[scoffs]
I wonder if it's fun being
as smart as you. Sharon.
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
I'm just
not having a great week.
This your first yoga class?
Pretty obvious. huh?
Looks good on you.
That's a very kind lie.
Thank you.
[cellphone vibrates]
[grunts]
Hey. what's up?
[Tillman] Townsend
just took a call
from Lafayette Jewelers.
He says there's someone
hanging around
the outside of the store
who's all wrong.
Sounds like our guy. Lou.
Why would he be our guy?
[Tillman] Well. he's a half
mile from the 101.
And the owner says
there's also a suspicious car
across the street.
What's he driving?
[Tillman] It's a dark one
with blacked out windows.
Just like the one we found.
This could be our guy. Lou.
All right. I'm on my way.
Make sure Townsend doesn't
beat you there. all right?
[dispatcher]
Unit Sunset La Brea.
now got three multiple calls.
[Townsend] On the ground.
On the ground right now!
Police. stop!
Hands in the air.
[both] On the ground!
On the ground now!
- Don't look... Come here!
- [gunshot]
[alarm blaring]
No. no. no. no. no.
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
[woman] Police shot him!
Fuck!
Does he have a weapon?
No. I didn't see one.
- Stand back!
- [woman exclaims]
[woman] Stay back!
[Tillman] You think it's him?
[Lou] No. it's a fucking kid.
[sirens blaring]
[Lou] Call an RA.
Hey. hey. hey! Hey.
Hey. stand back.
Hey. call an RA.
- [Tillman] Get back.
- [Lou sighs]
[Lou] Wake up. Townsend.
What are you doing?
Cuff him.
Control. we got
an officer-involved shooting.
- [Tillman] Lou. Lou.
- [Lou] What?
He says...
He says it's his car.
[Lou] Which car?
The black one.
He says it's his car. man.
[dispatcher] 998.
what's your 20?
Roll an RA.
[dispatcher] Copy that.
1423 Grand.
What are you doing?
- He had a gun.
- What?
- He had a fucking gun.
- What are you talking about?
- Hey! He had a fucking gun.
- What?
See for yourself.
Control. it's Four King 79.
Be advised. Shots fired.
Suspect is down.
Suspect was armed
with a semi-automatic handgun.
What's the ETA on that RA?
[Stewart] You think
maybe your little theory
got in everyone's head
a little too much today?
[scoffs]
You got about 30 minutes
before the shooting
board arrives.
At this stage.
you just need to get
your statement straight.
Yeah. he hadn't drawn.
- You sure about that?
- Gun was still in his bag.
Well. then we have a problem.
I don't wanna bury anybody.
but I saw what I saw.
We have a problem
because your statement
won't tally
with Detective Townsend's.
Oh yeah? Well. that's
not exactly a big surprise
- considering...
- Or your partner's.
Tillman's account
agrees with Townsend's.
Suspect was gun-in-hand
about to fire
on a police officer.
And when times are difficult.
we pull together.
The three of you are suspended
until the investigation's
concluded.
After which time
you'll be welcome back.
Unless...
one man should choose
a different path.
[Mark] Congratulations
are in order.
Madeleine wrote her
first policy here at L and V.
She brought
Monroe in on estate
and she brought Monroe in...
on a significant coverage
on that wedding
at the Beverly Wilshire.
It's a great start. Madeleine.
[Madeleine exclaims]
- Congratulations.
- Oh. my God.
Shouldn't have.
- All right.
- [Madeleine] A mini boo.
Thank you.
- [applause]
- [exclaims]
[laughter]
[Mark] Good start. Madeleine.
Keep up the good work.
He actually wants
to extend cover
to the wedding favors
as well. yeah.
[Brian] What's he giving 'em?
Diamonds for the bridal party.
Around 12 carat each.
So that's an extra
five and a half mil.
[Phil] Oof! That's nice...
- [Madeleine] Yeah.
- [Phil] ...but also high-risk.
Make sure they have
a good security plan. yeah?
- Of course. I'm already on it.
- All right.
[Mark] I think
that's it. everybody.
Madeleine. good start.
Sharon. wanna
hold back for five
- real quick?
- Yeah. sure.
[Mark clears throat]
- Doing okay?
- Yeah.
- Good.
- [Sharon] Good.
Uh... I finally
was able to wrangle
the partners...
Um. so I just
wanted to fill you in.
Oh. good.
- Yeah.
- Great.
So the thinking is.
given the year that we had.
we're gonna put a pin in it
until early next year.
We really wanna get
a clear financial picture
of everything
before we make a decision.
- Okay? So. hang tight.
- [Sharon] Really?
- Yeah.
- Because...
it was my understanding
that we had
a really good financial year.
I mean. not least thanks to...
several of the policies
that I wrote.
I mean.
I can show you the numbers.
Yeah. we looked
at the numbers.
and that's why. come January
we think you're
gonna be pretty happy
but you gotta hang in there
until then.
Well. you said
that last January.
Well. good things come
to those who wait. Sharon.
But I've been waiting.
I've been here
for 11 years. Mark.
I'm aware.
Right. And you made...
junior partner in five
and senior in seven. So...
What's your question. Sharon?
My question is...
if it's not gonna happen.
then I just would like
to know that
so I can start
considering myself.
And maybe my clients.
That's all.
Oh. you mean
go to a competitor?
Well. I mean. I'm just saying.
You think
one of our competitors
is just gonna snatch you up
because you're gonna present
them the numbers?
I got a number for you.
Sharon. 53.
It's not a good number
for a woman
in this business. is it?
Because we know what those
rich guys are really buying
and it's not 53.
Don't threaten me.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[man] I think we got a hole
in the chain of custody.
[forensics officer]
I got Tillman's DNA match.
Which one's his desk?
I can take that.
Yeah.
-[ominous music playing]
- Huh.
- [waves crashing]
- [Sharon breathes deeply]
[sighs]
[exhales deeply]
[indistinct chatter]
[phone chimes]
- You okay?
- [Davis] Yeah.
[indistinct chattering]
[Sharon] There's a courier
coming in from Antwerp.
He's carrying watches and gems
for a billionaire
who's getting married.
Wedding favors.
With the value
of $5.5 million.
Where?
The Beverly Wilshire.
What's the security setup?
We insist that armed security
stay with our courier
until the transaction
is completed.
And there's one more thing...
the buyer is paying cash
for everything.
This way. he doesn't pay tax
and the vendor doesn't
have to declare it to the IRS.
You're looking at 11 million
dollars in that room.
Of which...
I want three.
Is there separate security
for the cash?
I don't know.
We don't insure the cash.
- So there could be.
- Could be.
That's a lot of guns.
- And it's a busy location.
- [sighs]
I'd say it's too risky.
Can I ask you something?
Have you ever done a job
for 11 million dollars?
No. I haven't.
Isn't that what you guys call
"walk away" money?
Well. that's the thing about
"walk away" money
is you gotta be able
to walk away with it.
What made you
change your mind anyway?
[sighs] Maybe there
comes a moment
when you realize
you don't have as much time
as you thought you had.
[reporter] Good looking
morning in the Southland.
unless you're on the 405
in south LA.
If you're headed southbound.
you know what I'm talking
there around Avalon.
It's the Avalon off-ramp
that's been shut down.
Now. CHP's calling that
an animal hazard...
[radio host] One third
of the body's
lymphatic system
is in the face.
- [cat meows]
- I know.
This is our new home.
- Go on.
- [cat meows]
[waves crashing]
[sighs]
[reporter] Okay.
you're in the valley.
you're trying to get
into Hollywood...
you're taking
101 southbound side
right there at Highland...
right near the Hollywood...
[door squeaks]
[Lou] Ah...
- Can I help you?
- [Lou] Good evening. ma'am.
I'm. uh. Detective Lubesnik
from the LAPD.
I got this address
as a last known domicile
for a man
by the name of James Davis.
Does that name
mean anything to you?
Why would you
be looking for him here?
You know Mr. Davis?
Why you looking for him?
- [treadmill whirring]
- [thudding]
[phone dings]
[treadmill stops]
[AI voice] You have
one forwarded message.
[Anne] James.
It's Anne. sweetheart.
I don't know
if this number works
but I'd like
to speak with you.
Will you call me if you can?
[breathing heavily]
[man on TV] And it's all yours
if the price is right!
Okay. boys...
it's bedtime.
Come on. let's go.
Come on. gentlemen.
Say good night.
- [boys] Good night.
- Night.
[man on TV] I'm gonna
go $22.51.
[host on TV] $22.51.
George. let's not
waste any more time.
Why don't you
leave your number?
- Yeah. All right.
- [host on TV] Say hello
to your new SUV!
- [telephone rings]
- [woman screaming over TV]
[host on TV] It's the Ford
Escape Active!
Featuring a 1.5 liter engine.
AC. automatic transmission...
[Anne] Hello?
James?
Hello?
Is everything okay?
[Anne] A man came to...
look for you.
A policeman.
He's concerned
about your safety.
Hello. James.
[sighs]
- [knocks]
- [exclaims]
Jesus Christ!
Hi.
Listen. uh. the courier.
when does he fly?
What?
The courier you were
telling me about.
when's he fly?
I don't... I don't know.
Days or weeks?
Well... [sighs]
the wedding is on Sunday.
so I'm guessing
Friday or Saturday.
Take this. Keep it on.
After we speak.
take out the SIM.
destroy it.
then dispose of the phone.
Seriously?
Isn't this what you want?
[Davis] Hi. I was wondering
if it would be possible
to take a look
at the wedding suite?
Let me see
what I can show you.
[security] Hold there. please.
Just a minute.
Hold. please.
- [phone ringing]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [Sharon] Yes.
- Yeah. I need you to get me
the flight number.
And the security guard.
I need a name.
[breathes deeply]
- [thudding]
- [grunting]
[cracks. snaps]
[telephone ringing]
[lock clicks]
- [thuds]
- [exclaims]
Everything I have of value
is in the...
[Ormon] Shut the fuck up.
- [thuds]
- [Sharon groans]
You can have it!
- You can have it!
- [Ormon] I'm not fucking here
for that. okay?
You know what I'm here for.
Hey. stay the fuck still.
All right?
You know what I want.
[Sharon] What? No. I don't.
No. I don't.
[Ormon] I'm not
fuckin' dumb. bitch.
[Sharon] I have
no idea what you want!
[Ormon] Huh? Don't fucking...
You're gonna fucking give me
what you gave him.
you get to keep your face.
- Yeah.
- Yes. yes. yes.
[Ormon] You want
to keep your face?
You tell me
what you fucking gave him.
- Okay. Okay.
- [Ormon] Okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
[Ormon] You're gonna
tell me what you gave him.
[yoga instructor] And.
when you're ready
coming up
into a seated position.
[indistinct chatter]
Not in the mood today?
Can I buy you a coffee?
Or maybe a smoothie?
Is everything okay?
Oh...
What happened?
And what did you tell
the guy who attacked you?
I told him
everything I told you.
Same as you told this "Mike"?
Yeah.
Seeing as
I told you all this...
is that gonna
keep me outta jail?
[Lou scoffs]
You basically confessed
to conspiracy
to commit gross larceny.
Yeah.
We go official with this.
you're in...
Well. it gets ugly.
Fuck!
[sighs]
You have somewhere
you can stay for a few days?
Friend. maybe?
You can stay at my place.
It'd be safe.
[sighs]
Tell me more
about this "Mike."
[indistinct chatter]
- Hey.
- [officer] Hey.
How you doing? I need
to review the evidence from
that case from last week.
- Ah.
- Here you go.
It's late.
You... You know where it is?
'Cause I'm closing up in ten.
I'll just be... It won't
be more than five minutes.
- Five minutes?
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Thanks.
[door release buzzing]
[officer] Five minutes.
Thank you.
[exhales deeply]
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah. Um...
I gotta go outta town
for a while.
Why?
Just a work thing.
This opportunity has come up.
and I have to go.
For how long?
Not sure exactly.
You know. could be a while.
- Yeah. so...
- [Maya] Uh-huh...
Can you do me a favor?
What's that?
Can you just
tell me the truth?
[chuckles]
That is the truth.
Okay.
And...
what is it that you do?
I told you.
Hey. can I grab a drink?
[waiter] Sure.
Give me a second.
[Maya] Look at me.
Look at me or I'm leaving.
Do you know
how fucked up this is?
I mean. I'm...
I'm walking around...
thinking that I...
Thinking about
how much I like you.
And then I realize
I don't even know you.
I mean.
you haven't told me anything.
There are no photographs
of your past.
You seem to have no family.
You have no friends.
You have...
There's... There's nothing.
[sighs] Maya. I'm just
asking you to wait for me.
[Maya] Wait?
For what?
No. seriously. for what?
For you to get
to some magic number?
Don't patronize me.
Just 'cause you don't
understand. it doesn't matter?
What. money?
Yeah. If you grow up
with no money
then you don't have
any choices.
And then bad shit happens.
Bad things
come into your life.
[Maya] What kind of bad shit?
Bad people.
I'm just asking you
to wait a short time.
I'm not where I need
to be yet. okay?
I think you are.
[door opens. closes]
[imperceptible]
[tense music playing]
[phone chimes and vibrates]
[clicks]
Wow.
Look at you.
Pretending to be a capitalist?
[chuckles]
Something like that.
How'd you sleep?
- Good.
- [Lou] Yeah.
I have some coffee up there.
There's some
oat milk in the fridge.
Thank you.
Well. make yourself at home.
[elevator bell dings]
[car lock beeps]
[indistinct chatter]
[sighs]
[plane engine roaring]
[knocks]
- Yeah.
- [Davis] Hey. sorry.
I'm here for a pickup.
My phone's about to die.
You don't have a charger
that I could borrow. do you?
I do. buddy. but I'm...
Hands on
the steering wheel. Bob.
[Nelson] Please.
don't hurt my family.
Start by handing me
your phone.
[attendant] Please be careful
when opening
the overhead bins.
Items may have shifted during
flight and could fall out.
You may continue
to use the cellular function.
[official] Mr. Foster?
Yes?
[official] Please follow me.
What's this about?
[indistinct announcement
over PA]
[car locks beep]
[Davis] Mr. Foster?
Welcome.
All right. you're good to go?
Can I see some ID?
Sure.
Thanks.
Here you go. Good to go.
- Your flight okay?
- Huh?
Yeah. yeah. thanks.
Pretty used to it by now.
Come out this way a lot?
[Lou] Ah. you know.
few times a year.
Lot of homeless here. huh?
I could be dirt poor.
you wouldn't catch me
living on the sidewalk.
What's that saying?
Don't judge a man till you
walked a mile in his shoes.
I wore those shoes once.
They didn't suit me too well.
Where'd you say you're from?
I'm from here.
LA.
Whereabouts?
Bunch of places.
Moved around a lot as a kid.
It's a nice car.
You like cars?
[Davis] Yeah. I prefer
the old American ones.
How about yourself?
[Lou] When I was a kid.
I dreamt
about having a Mustang.
Like Steve McQueen.
Yeah. [chuckles]
Yeah. Steve McQueen.
It's funny. a guy your age
wouldn't normally know
who Steve McQueen is.
I grew up
watching those movies.
What's your favorite?
Uh. say. uh...
Bullitt. you know. the chases.
Yeah.
Yeah. mine's
Thomas Crown Affair.
McQueen plays
a high-class thief.
I didn't catch that one.
[indistinct chatter]
[chuckles]
Hey. Sharon.
[Sharon] Madeleine.
you don't have to do this.
You don't have to laugh
at his silly little jokes
or even act like you like him
or anything here
because that's what I did
for years and years.
And they told me exactly
what they're telling you.
that I was the brightest spark
to ever be interviewed.
That they were waiting
for somebody like me
to walk through that door.
They said that I would
make partner
and that I would have equity
- that I would be set for life.
- Okay.
And then they
dragged it on forever
- as if they were...
- [Mark] Sounds like you're
having an HR problem...
There's a protocol for that...
- and this is not it.
- You know what?
- This is...
- Shut the fuck up.
You know what else?
They don't care
how smart you are.
They don't care what you know
or how good you are.
All you are to them is bait.
Bait to land the next big.
fat. rich fish.
that these assholes
can't land for themselves.
Now. I don't know
how many years
that I'm gonna have left
to offer since I'm "53."
But I do know.
that I'm not
gonna give 'em to you.
[breathing heavily]
[indistinct chatter]
Private security.
visiting a guest
in the wedding suite.
That's fine.
Go right ahead. sir.
Hey. it's my first day.
I'm supposed
to be on butler service.
Ah. fifth floor.
Just down on the end here.
Been here before?
Yes. I have.
[clang. crash]
[man] Stop. Jamie. stop.
[elevator bell dings]
I'd take the next one.
please. folks.
[man] Sorry.
[Ormon] Hey. I. uh. forgot
which room
I gotta take this to.
It'll be on the ticket.
First day. I don't know
what I did with it.
Dial 0-1-1.
All right.
[phone trilling]
Hey. I got drinks for Monroe.
I think they gave me
the wrong room number.
[elevator bell dings]
Mr. Monroe?
I'm gonna call you back.
- Babe?
- That's... Yeah?
- Some guys here for you.
- [Monroe] Okay. good.
Uh. no. I want it as-is.
- Antwerp?
- That's right.
Okay. I gotta go.
Yeah. no. I gotta go.
- Any problems?
- Uh. no. sir.
[Monroe] No issues
with customs?
All right. everyone.
hands on your head right now!
No one needs to get hurt!
What the fuck
do you think you're doing?
You two on your knees
facing the wall. right now.
- You're the security guy.
- He has a gun. He has a gun!
- Just... He has a gun.
- What is this?
It's a robbery.
- [Adrienne] Just...
- Hey. I'm not fucking around!
- On your knees right now!
- Who the fuck are you?
I'm not telling you again.
on your fucking knees!
- Please don't hurt me.
- [Monroe] Shit.
[Adrienne exclaiming]
[Adrienne panting]
Briefcase on the table. hands
on your head. then kneel.
Let's go.
All right. where's
the cash. Monroe?
[Monroe] Cash? What?
There's no fucking cash.
The cash you're using to pay
for your items in the case.
It's in the safe!
Where's the safe?
- Where's the fucking safe?
- It's over there!
It's to the left!
- [Davis] You know the code?
- No.
[Davis] All right. Monroe.
When I say so. you're gonna
crawl over to the safe.
Unlock. but do not open it.
And crawl back
to where you are now.
Understand?
- Yeah. Yeah. yeah. yeah.
- Move. Go.
Jesus fucking Christ.
It's right here.
Oh. shit. I fucked up.
I fucked up.
[Adrienne]
Just put the code in.
Stop messing around! Come on!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Okay. I got it.
- I'm not fucking playing!
- All right.
- Put in the fucking code!
- I'll put it in! Sorry!
Fuck. there it is! Fuck!
Hey you. fill this bag up.
[Monroe] Fuck.
[exhales deeply]
[Adrienne] Here.
Get back to where you were.
All right. Mr. Courier Man.
open the briefcase.
Come on. let's go.
[Lou] Has a combination.
That's okay. Nice and easy.
[elevator bell dings]
All right.
take the diamonds out.
[Monroe] Jesus
fucking Christ. man.
- What the fuck is happening?
- Hey. shut up.
- [Monroe] Shit. Jesus Christ!
- Shut up!
- Fuck. man.
- Stop fucking talking.
Put the gun down!
I'm a police officer.
- What?
- You're under arrest.
Put the gun down.
Second you pull that trigger.
I pull mine.
You probably
got a kid somewhere. right?
And for what? For this
fucking crooked prick?
[gun cocks]
[Lou] Put it down.
It's the last time
I'm asking you.
Put the gun down now. James.
I know all about you.
And I know you never
hurt anyone before.
You're pointing
the gun at a cop.
[Monroe] You're a cop?
- Then be a fucking cop.
- [Lou] Shut up.
- Stop fucking talking.
- Shoot the fucking guy.
[Monroe] Shoot him right now.
- We'll vouch for you!
- Shut up! Shut up!
[whispers] Fuck. Fuck you.
Put the gun down!
I'm not putting
the fucking gun down!
[Lou] This is the last time
I'm asking you!
[beeps]
Oh. fuck.
Put your fucking gun down!
- [Adrienne exclaims]
- Put your fucking gun down!
- [Adrienne] Oh. my God.
- Put your gun down!
Put your fucking gun down!
- Please. God.
- [Ormon] Put the gun down!
- Put the gun down!
- [Ormon] Who the fuck is he?
He's a cop. kid.
- You're a fucking cop?
- You're out of your depth.
[Ormon] Fucking cop!
Put your gun down!
Don't even fucking
- look at me. all right?
- [Davis] Fuck.
[grunts]
Put it down.
[Ormon] You think
I'm fucking playing?
You think I'm fucking playing?
- Listen to me.
- Hey.
Listen to me.
[spits] Pig. You fucking pig.
- [Lou] Put the gun down.
- I'm gonna start counting.
You want blood on your
motherfuckin' cop hands?
Put it down.
You want fucking blood
on your cop hands?
- You are a cop!
- One!
- Shut up!
- Be a fucking cop!
Shoot him now!
Shut up!
Fucking two!
You think I'm fucking playing?
- [gunshot]
- [Adrienne screams]
[Ormon] Fuck you! Fuck you!
Yeah!
You think I'm fuckin' playing?
[Adrienne] Oh. my God.
[Ormon] Fucking piece of shit.
Fuck you. [spits] Fuck you.
Just take
what you came for and go.
[Ormon] Fucking pig.
[Monroe groans]
[Ormon] Push
the case towards me.
Push the fucking case
toward me!
[Adrienne hyperventilating]
[Lou] Just take it.
- Don't fucking look at me.
- Not looking at you.
[Ormon] Yes. you are.
You've seen my face. so...
I need you
to put your gun down.
Put your fucking gun down.
- Come on.
- [Lou] Can't.
[Ormon] Put the gun down.
Gun down.
Put the fucking gun down!
[Lou] I'm not
putting the gun down.
No. Hey. put the gun down.
Come on.
Put the fucking gun down!
Put it down!
- Fuck you!
- [gunshot]
[Adrienne and Monroe scream]
[Monroe] Oh. shit!
Holy fuck!
Oh. my God.
[Adrienne hyperventilating]
Oh. my God!
[Monroe] He's fucking...
He's dead.
[exclaims]
[Davis] Oh. fuck.
He was gonna shoot you.
Shit.
Here's what you're gonna do.
You're gonna get in your car
and you're gonna
drive and never come back.
The money and the diamonds
are still there.
There's the thief.
The 101 Robber.
I didn't wanna shoot him.
[Lou] I know.
[Monroe] Oh. shit. Oh. my God.
Hey...
I need a fuckin'
ambulance right now.
I'm gonna personally ensure
that you do time.
You're never
gonna work ever again.
No. you're not.
You're gonna keep
your money and your stones.
And when the cops
show up here.
you're gonna
listen to what I tell 'em.
and then you're gonna say.
"What he said."
The fuck I will.
See. once they
start investigating you
for the importation of illegal
stones and tax evasion
then they
really start digging.
So you better be
squeaky fucking clean.
Is that what you want?
[Adrienne] What the fuck
is the matter with you?
The fuck
[sighs]
Fuck.
I suggest you get
all that back in the safe
before my colleagues arrive.
[groans]
- Call me a fucking ambulance.
- [Adrienne] Fucking coward.
No.
This is Detective Lubesnik.
Robbery Division.
I'm at the Beverly Wilshire.
room 1018.
I need a RA unit.
I have two victims down.
One KMA.
another breathing.
but suffering from a gunshot
wound to the shoulder.
[sirens blaring]
[yoga instructor] Inhale...
Exhale.
You are safe.
You are calm.
You are exactly
where you need to be.
[breathing heavily]
Open yourself to the truth
of what's within you.
Don't hold back.
[engine revving]
It's now time
to slowly begin to bring
your awareness back...
into the physical body.
[breathes deeply]
[exhales]
May you have
a beautiful rest of your day.
Namaste.
[people] Namaste.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey.
I came by your apartment.
Uh. yeah. I was away.
Yeah. I had a message.
- Oh. yeah? I. uh...
- Mmm...
I have something for you.
Maybe don't open that in here.
Why? What is it?
Something
nobody's looking for.
You said you have
a message for me. too.
[inhales. sighs]
This was sent to me.
Yeah. I don't know
what that is.
No?
Well...
you think you'll be...
coming back to yoga?
I don't know.
Think I should?
I think you should.
All right.
- See ya.
[elevator dings]
[mellow music playing]
[music turns dramatic]
[clinks]
[exhales sharply]
[engine starts]
[laughs]
[music fades]
[upbeat music playing]
[intriguing music playing]
[music continues]
[music fades]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org